

Peter Marinov

Lead PHY Integration and Verification Engineer

Passionate verification engineer with more than 8 years of experience in PHY integrations and verification. Proven ability to establish and maintain excellent communication and relationships with other teams and customers.

peter.marinov91@gmail.com



+359879006781



Sofia, Bulgaria

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead MTS Verification Engineer Rambus

03/2022 - Present Sofia, Bulgaria

In addition to the previous responsibilities:

- Improving the workflow

Senior Design and Verification Engineer Rambus

08/2021 - 02/2022 Rambus acquired PLDA Sofia, Bulgaria

Senior Design and Verification Engineer **PLDA**

03/2021 - 07/2021 Sofia, Bulgaria

In addition to the previous responsibilities:

- Training new people in the team
- Creating projects schedules
- Leading customers/partners meetings
- Reciting and leading interviews for new members for the company

Verification Engineer PLDA

03/2014 - 02/2021 Sofia, Bulgaria

Responsibilities:

- PHY integrations
- Debugging and reporting issues
- IP verification of PCIe MAC
- Creating and updating test cases
- Customer support
- Creating release packages for customers
- Creating and maintaining documentations
- Collecting metrics
- Creating and leading training for internship students
- Create and maintain scripts

SKILLS



EDUCATION

Bachelor of Electronic Engineering Technical University

09/2010 - 06/2016

Sofia, Bulgaria

Thesis:

 Micro process system for measuring air temperature and absolute pressure

LANGUAGES

Bulgarian Native or Bilingual Proficiency English

Professional Working Proficiency

German

Elementary Proficiency